{
  "1": [
    {
      "question": "Ann's room is _____ than Dan's .",
      "correctAnswer": "cleaner",
      "incorrectAnswers": "more clean"
    },
    {
      "question": "Kim's dress is _____ than Emma's . ",
      "correctAnswer": "dirtier",
      "incorrectAnswers": "more dirty"
    },
    {
      "question": "A cake is _____ than an orange .",
      "correctAnswer": "sweeter",
      "incorrectAnswers": "more sweet"
    },
    {
      "question": "A cat is _____ than a crocodile .",
      "correctAnswer": "nicer",
      "incorrectAnswers": "more nice"
    },
    {
      "question": "Jill is _____ than Max .",
      "correctAnswer": "more active",
      "incorrectAnswers": "activer"
    },
    {
      "question": "Sam is _____ than Ken .",
      "correctAnswer": "braver",
      "incorrectAnswers": "more brave"
    },
    {
      "question": "She is _____ than her father .",
      "correctAnswer": "calmer",
      "incorrectAnswers": "more calm"
    },
    {
      "question": "My book is _____ than his book .",
      "correctAnswer": "more interesting",
      "incorrectAnswers": "interestinger"
    },
    {
      "question": "Juice is _____ than water .",
      "correctAnswer": "tastier",
      "incorrectAnswers": "more tasty"
    },
    {
      "question": "My car is _____ than your car .",
      "correctAnswer": "slower",
      "incorrectAnswers": "more slow"
    },
    {
      "question": "He is _____ than his brother .",
      "correctAnswer": "greedier",
      "incorrectAnswers": "more greedy"
    },
    {
      "question": "Tim is _____ than Tom .",
      "correctAnswer": "taller",
      "incorrectAnswers": "more tall"
    },
    {
      "question": "My room is _____ than my parents' room .",
      "correctAnswer": "smaller",
      "incorrectAnswers": "more small"
    },
    {
      "question": "Mary is _____ than Dina .",
      "correctAnswer": "plumper",
      "incorrectAnswers": "more plump"
    },
    {
      "question": "My brother is _____ than her brother .",
      "correctAnswer": "more handsome",
      "incorrectAnswers": "handsomer"
    },
    {
      "question": "This book is _____ than that one . ",
      "correctAnswer": "thinner",
      "incorrectAnswers": "more thin"
    },
    {
      "question": "Our teacher is the _____ teacher in our school .",
      "correctAnswer": "kindest",
      "incorrectAnswers": "most kind"
    },
    {
      "question": "She is the _____ girl in our class .",
      "correctAnswer": "prettiest",
      "incorrectAnswers": "most pretty"
    },
    {
      "question": "He is the _____ boy in our school !",
      "correctAnswer": "rudest",
      "incorrectAnswers": "most rude"
    },
    {
      "question": "My mum is the _____ woman in our family .",
      "correctAnswer": "most serious",
      "incorrectAnswers": "seriousnest"
    },
    {
      "question": "I have many books and this is the _____ one .",
      "correctAnswer": "thickest",
      "incorrectAnswers": "most thick"
    },
    {
      "question": "July is the _____ month .",
      "correctAnswer": "hottest",
      "incorrectAnswers": "most hot"
    },
    {
      "question": "January is the _____ month .",
      "correctAnswer": "coldest",
      "incorrectAnswers": "most cold"
    },
    {
      "question": "Our house is the _____ one on our street .",
      "correctAnswer": "biggest",
      "incorrectAnswers": "most big"
    },
    {
      "question": "My room is the _____ one in our flat .",
      "correctAnswer": "smallest",
      "incorrectAnswers": "most small"
    },
    {
      "question": "My sister is the _____ girl in our school .",
      "correctAnswer": "most beautiful",
      "incorrectAnswers": "beautifulest"
    },
    {
      "question": "She has the _____ hair in our family .",
      "correctAnswer": "longest",
      "incorrectAnswers": "most long"
    },
    {
      "question": "This exercise is the _____ one .",
      "correctAnswer": "easiest",
      "incorrectAnswers": "most easy"
    },
    {
      "question": "She is the _____ girl in the class .",
      "correctAnswer": "cleverest",
      "incorrectAnswers": "most clever"
    }
  ],
  "2": [
    {
      "question": "Your room is _____ # than my room .",
      "correctAnswer": "cleaner",
      "incorrectAnswers": "most cleaner"
    },
    {
      "question": "Kim's socks are _____ # than Sam's socks .",
      "correctAnswer": "dirtier",
      "incorrectAnswers": "dirtiest"
    },
    {
      "question": "A pie is _____ # than an apple .",
      "correctAnswer": "sweeter",
      "incorrectAnswers": "sweetest"
    },
    {
      "question": "A rabbit is _____ # than a frog .",
      "correctAnswer": "nicer",
      "incorrectAnswers": "nicest"
    },
    {
      "question": "Sam is the _____ # boy in my class .",
      "correctAnswer": "most active",
      "incorrectAnswers": "more active"
    },
    {
      "question": "My dog is the _____ # animal in the world !",
      "correctAnswer": "bravest",
      "incorrectAnswers": "most brave"
    },
    {
      "question": "She is _____ # than her brother .",
      "correctAnswer": "calmer",
      "incorrectAnswers": "calmest"
    },
    {
      "question": "Victor is _____ # than Emma .",
      "correctAnswer": "friendlier",
      "incorrectAnswers": "more friendly"
    },
    {
      "question": "This book is _____ # than that one .",
      "correctAnswer": "more interesting",
      "incorrectAnswers": "most interesting"
    },
    {
      "question": "A banana is _____ # than a lemon .",
      "correctAnswer": "tastier",
      "incorrectAnswers": "tastiest"
    },
    {
      "question": "A car is _____ # than a plane .",
      "correctAnswer": "slower",
      "incorrectAnswers": "slowest"
    },
    {
      "question": "Max is the _____ # boy in our class .",
      "correctAnswer": "tallest",
      "incorrectAnswers": "taller"
    },
    {
      "question": "Pam is the _____ # boy in our school .",
      "correctAnswer": "greediest",
      "incorrectAnswers": "greedier"
    },
    {
      "question": "A mouse is _____ # than an elephant .",
      "correctAnswer": "smaller",
      "incorrectAnswers": "smallest"
    },
    {
      "question": "Betty is _____ # than Veronica .",
      "correctAnswer": "plumper",
      "incorrectAnswers": "plumpest"
    },
    {
      "question": "Ken is the _____ # boy in our class .",
      "correctAnswer": "most handsome",
      "incorrectAnswers": "more handsome"
    },
    {
      "question": "My book is _____ # than her book .",
      "correctAnswer": "thinner",
      "incorrectAnswers": "thinnest"
    },
    {
      "question": "My teacher is the _____ # teacher in our school .",
      "correctAnswer": "kindest",
      "incorrectAnswers": "kinder"
    },
    {
      "question": "Ella is the _____ # girl in my class .",
      "correctAnswer": "prettiest",
      "incorrectAnswers": "prettier"
    },
    {
      "question": "Luc is _____ # than Alex .",
      "correctAnswer": "ruder",
      "incorrectAnswers": "rudest"
    },
    {
      "question": "My grandfather is the _____ # man in our family .",
      "correctAnswer": "most serious",
      "incorrectAnswers": "more serious"
    },
    {
      "question": "Today is the _____ # day of the year .",
      "correctAnswer": "hottest",
      "incorrectAnswers": "hotter"
    },
    {
      "question": "His book is _____ # than my book .",
      "correctAnswer": "thicker",
      "incorrectAnswers": "thickest"
    },
    {
      "question": "September is not the _____ # month of the year .",
      "correctAnswer": "coldest",
      "incorrectAnswers": "colder"
    },
    {
      "question": "Her backpack is _____ # than my backpack .",
      "correctAnswer": "bigger",
      "incorrectAnswers": "biggest"
    },
    {
      "question": "My mum is the _____ # woman in the world !",
      "correctAnswer": "most beautiful",
      "incorrectAnswers": "more beautiful"
    },
    {
      "question": "Her hair is _____ # than Pam's hair .",
      "correctAnswer": "longer",
      "incorrectAnswers": "longest"
    },
    {
      "question": "This task is the _____ # one .",
      "correctAnswer": "easiest",
      "incorrectAnswers": "easier"
    }
  ]
}